I've been following Atolye15 for a long time.
The things they do in Izmir is truly beautiful.
I actually gave the said presentation about Flexible Grid System at Atolye15, too.
They took it pretty well. I'm sending a mail to a firm in Izmir.
Saying that I have this project and I want to show it to them.
They graciously inviting me to their office and I'm giving a presentation to them.
They are such a gracious firm and open to new technologies.
To be honest, I was pretty happy with the fact that there is such a firm in Izmir.
That they treat us like one of their own and providing opportunities eventhough we were strangers to them.
Also WTK was pretty awesome. They filled that lack of conferences in Izmir.
It's awesome because people can meet and stay in touch with many others here.
They get to know about new things in industry.
The first presentation was pretty good.
I'm sure the rest will be, as well.
Special thanks to Atolye15 for everything.